Hey.
Are you the one who beat my boys?
This is not possible.
Hey, get up, get up, okay?
These are my guys.
Stand up straight, motherfucker.
Is it possible to lower morale?
You guys are, like, the coolest second years.
Why are you being beaten?
Sorry.
If you join our gang, I will forgive you.
And if not, then you will receive
in full until our graduation.
What do you choose? To be with us?
Sorry.
Don't want to?
Hey, hey!
Not answering? A? Bastard, answer!
Answer again! What did you say?
Don't want.
You bastards!
Take your hands off! Aren't you going to answer?
A? Don't you want to?
Yes.
"Yes"?
You bastard!
Let me pass.
Now I'll show you something.
Brazilian kick.
Stand up straight, like this.
Stand up straight.
Right.
Brazilian kick!
I can't lift my leg high.
You need to go even higher, stand up straight.
Straight up, like this.
Tighten your muscles here.
Tighten up!
Low kick!
A kick is a low kick!
We'll have your back
so get money out of the kids
and give us 100 thousand a week.
Take the rest for yourself.
OK?
Don't want.
No ho...
You don't want to, bastard, do you?
Get up.
Don't you want to?
Come here.
Stand here.
Don't you want to? Don't you want to? Do you dare snap back?
These are the scum.
Stand up straight, idiot.
He removed his hands.
I said get your hands off you bastard!
Hurt.
Hey.
Still held up well.
Why bother with people like that?
I just let myself be beaten.
Exactly, exactly.
Jerk.
It won’t even fit into a fist...
I almost died, really.
Are you okay?
Look at your face.
These are the scum.
Oh those bastards.
I told you to collect money
and you ignore
no matter how much you call
don't appear, hide.
What about you?
Have you played in a computer club?
Oh, really, damn it.
Are you crazy, bastard? A?
Are you crazy?
Hey.
Did you play with the money you collected?
Give me the money you collected here, quickly.
Fast.
One, two.
24 thousand won?
How many?
He only has 24 thousand won.
Cute.
Are you sure you put everything together correctly?
Isn't this your money?
No.
Exactly?
Yes.
Hey, what about you?
I have no.
What?
No?
I didn't extort money.
Wow.
Hey, you're brave.
Are you crazy?
Totally crazy, you bastard.
Are you kidding me?
Hey.
What?
You go.
I'm letting you go, go.
Just go away.
Let's go.
Only you.
What?
Do you want to stay instead of him?
Go.
Get out of here!
It's okay, go ahead.
Get lost!
What a schmuck.
He's really leaving.
One, two, three.
Are you running away today?
You have to leave when they let you go.
You're good at running away.
As always, right?
So how? So how?
Do memories come flooding back? A? Well, damn it.
We played so much fun, right?
Damn, no fun.
Just lie down.
Why are you trying to get up?
Hey!
Stop it.
Superhero.
I came because I was interested.
Well, ask something.
Why are you...
Are you beating up my people?
Do you want...
help him take revenge?
You will become disabled today because of him.
Understand?
This bastard doesn't know anything, huh?
Hey Kang Yoon.
Do you have no conscience at all?
Your friend will become disabled today
You need to at least explain the reason.
I don't care about your problems.
I just don't like you.
That's why I just want to beat you.
Are you blocking a blow?
Funny.
Is it my turn now?
Are you blocking again?
Are you blocking, are you blocking?
Are you blocking?
Hey.
Get up.
Block it, damn it!
Hey.
You have this...
broke.
I really felt it.
This is where it broke.
This is why you need to choose your friends well.
Otherwise, this is how you will become disabled.
Kang Yun.
And revenge
only strong bastards do it.
Because of you
today your friend will become disabled.
Stop it!
Lee Gwije?
Long time no see.
I didn't even know you were in Yongseong.
I said stop.
Enough means enough.
What if I don't want to?
Then I'll force you.
Hey superhero!
See you later.
Come get it.
And you too finish already.
Kang Yoongi.
Don't bother me anymore.
I repaid the debt.
Wrong.
Why are you always
making the same mistakes?
Don't want to concentrate?
Don't you want to?
Again.
- Yes.
- Again.
Turn around.
I don't hit you out of anger
so don't be offended.
There is very little left.
From what you do now,
your future life will depend.
Under no circumstances should you
live in such a way that you are despised like a dad.
Do you understand me?
Yes.
I love you.
Eugyom!
You know how hard it is for me?
You know.
Eugyom.
- Don't come, don't come.
- You know.
Mother!
Sugyeom, what happened?
You
I didn’t intentionally want to hurt my brother,
right?
Eugyeom will understand everything too.
Everything is fine.
Sugyeom.
Until the goal is achieved
There's very little left.
Let's be patient a little longer, okay?
Almost everything.
Now it's all over.
- Uigyom...
- Blood.
-Are you okay?
- Don't come closer.
Eugyom, I'm sorry, I...
- My mind is a little clouded...
- Get out of here!
Hey!
Why is it so noisy?
What time is it?
Sugyeom.
Quickly go to your room.
Now the brother is very irritated.
There is very little left.
So, Sugyeom?
You did a good job.
Sugyeom, congratulations.
I knew you could do it.
Congratulations to Uygyom too
Welcome to Seomun High School!
Thank you.
So.
For our family!
Hooray!
Congratulations brother.
I'm very proud of you.
Mother.
Yes?
Can I quit school?
What are you talking about?
- Mom, I...
- Sugyeom.
Mom has a lot of work today.
I need to finish this today.
I...
very hard.
Are you quitting medical school?
Why?
Are you out of your mind right now?
This is just the beginning, why?!
Eugyom.
Are you sleeping?
This...
I wanted to give it to you
because this is the most valuable thing,
what I have.
But...
after dad threw them,
they broke.
No sound.
But even if there is no sound,
when I put them on,
I feel calm in my soul.
When you put them on,
you can find yourself in a world where there is no dad.
Eugyom.
Forgive me for everything.
You again?
- Fell down the stairs again?
- Uigyom.
It's all my fault.
Eugyeom, are you okay?
Are you feeling better now?
Eugyom.
Who did it?
These bastards, are they bandits or what?
How can you do this?
Who is this?
I will put everyone in prison for a long time.
You know too, right?
Who is this?
Expensive.
Eugyeom woke up.
Let's take care of our son first.
Kim Namhyup.
Who?
Kim Namhyup sent.
Why does Namhyup need this?
I beat him up a little
because he is very bad
beats children and takes money.
- You...
- Dad.
Are you sure everything will be okay?
After all, this is the son of the hospital director,
where do you deliver the goods?
Jail.
Can you plant him?
Kang Yoongi.
Yes?
Aren't you ashamed in front of me?
Ashamed.
Because of your revenge, I even got into a fight.
Because of your revenge, I even...
portrayed this stupid hero.
Eugyom.
There is no need to apologize to me.
I told you so.
I don't care about your problems.
Just that bastard from Chinilgu
looked annoying
so I just wanted to beat him.
And he told me to come get the player.
Eugyom.
You can’t, you can’t go to him.
Let's get this over with.
Kang Yoongi.
Knowing that this is impossible,
why did you start?
Hello.
Sorry.
How is Eugyeom?
How is he feeling?
He's on sick leave.
Immediately after discharge
will go to America to study,
so don't call him anymore.
Kang Yoongi.
Is Eugyeom okay?
Don't know.
Seduced a diligent student
inciting him to fight,
and now that it's all over,
do you feel better?
After this you are still
do you consider yourself a friend?
Chison.
What, are you sitting? Are you okay already?
Who are you?
Here's a horse.
Look at your face.
By the way, what's wrong with your face?
Got into a fight again?
You scared me!
What's wrong with your face?
Are you okay already? Can you walk?
Not yet.
The nurse picked me up.
Get well soon.
We'll have to make up for lost time.
I was really bored, damn it.
But you're not mad at me?
Why?
It's because of me.
I ran away cowardly.
Do you still think so?
I felt so sorry for you.
I should have been there for you.
I was going to do this.
I saw you coming back.
That bastard is back.
Hey Lee Kiyun, you win.
I told you he'll be back.
This dog came to die.
Sucks.
Hey Lee Chisung.
Know that you're lucky today, huh?
I'll kill him instead of you.
- We agreed that we would let Yoongi go.
-Are you insolent to me?
What suddenly happened to him?
Let go.
Hold it.
Hold it!
Let go!
He gets up.
Flew!
Let me go!
Hey, hey, hey.
On the count of three, release.
If we let him go, he will die.
I said let go.
Stop it, bastards!
On the count of three, release. One, two, three.
On the count of three... Hey, on the count
three let go. One, two, three.
Hey!
I said let go, let go.
Crap.
What to do?
Kisu, damn it.
Understood?
It's not because of you that I became like this, you fool.
On the contrary, you saved me.
Did you go to the police station?
and he told you everything, right?
Thanks to this father
is going to file a lawsuit.
Kim Namhyup's father has power,
but thanks to your testimony
there is a chance to win.
You must have been scared and lonely.
I'm grateful to you.
Thank you, Yoongi.
Eugyom.
Are you sleeping?
Brother?
This...
I wanted to give it to you
because this is the most valuable thing,
what I have.
Brother.
Brother!
Eugyom.
Eugyom!
What are you doing there?
It's dangerous.
Please...
Come to mom.
Eugyom.
Mother.
I think I can understand brother now.
Eugyom.
Eigyom, mom is very sorry.
Mom is very sorry.
It's all Mom's fault.
Because of my greed...
Knowing that you and Sugyeom are suffering,
knowing that your dad is too cruel,
because of my greed
I just hoped
that you will do well.
Eugyom, I'm sorry.
Eugyom, I'm so sorry.
It's all my fault.
Mom was too greedy.
Eugyom.
Eigyom, come down.
Please come down.
Sorry.
It's too hard for me.
More me...
I can't stand it.
Eugyom...
Eugyom.
Eygyom, Ey...
Eigyom, thank you.
Thank you, Eugyeom.
Thank you!
Mom will try to become better.
Thank you, Eugyeom.
Eugyom.
I'll be better.
Sorry, thank you.
Eugyom.
Thank you.
Mom will protect you.
Eugyom.
Have you come?
Let's talk.
I talked to my grandfather.
You will go to America immediately after discharge.
You will be transferred to a school in Boston.
What are you talking about?
Wait.
Sit down.
Grandfather was right.
It was a mistake from the start
transfer to that school.
- Dad.
- Uigyom.
This is all for your own good.
This time completely
different environment...
You.
Let's talk.
Expensive.
Kim Seoktae.
Let's talk first.
I just almost lost our son.
What does it mean?
Your son
my son wanted to jump.
What?
Why?
You are unbearable.
You say this is for Uigyeom?
You?
No.
You have never in your life
you'll find out what it is.
From now on
I will protect my son.
Hey, in Panama!
Panama!
Does this bastard have blocked ears?
Doesn't answer, damn it.
Are you Lee Gwije?
Lee Gwije from Mumyeon?
He ignores us, scum.
Hello.
Have you come?
Don't pay attention to those behind you.
Come play with us.
Do you even see anything?
What a stubborn little rat he is.
Crap.
Hey.
That bastard's shoulder went off.
Finish it.
Hey.
How strong.
Have you gone through all of them?
The rumors didn't lie, Gwidzhe.
From now on it's just you and me.
You have a shoulder
I have an ankle.
Honestly, right?